That's mr Ryan Walker
leaving the NATO conference
to go awol with the
Russian foreign minister.
No official car. No ppos.
And no special adviser. Melissa Morris.
Does Ryan often go awol?
Does he shut you out of things?
That's not why I got into politics.
Why are you working
with Ryan Walker. then?
There is always room for
someone like you in our office.
Can we leave the cross-questioning
to the journalists. please?
Your colleagues say to
me that you should resign.
I won't be resigning any time soon.
Did you leak my meeting with
Dimitri krimsov to the press? No.
Do not meddle with
the Democratic process.
It is my great pleasure
to announce my campaign
to be the next leader of our
party and of our great country.
The man in the merc was lev
amatov. our cuddly British oligarch.
There's plenty of dirty money
in Montenegro. you know.
Why would Imogen accept
a 200-grand donation
from a man like lev amatov?
She spent an awful lot of time
horsing around with her aide.
Joshua long? Do you think
Imogen's ever been unfaithful?
No. not that I know of. Why?
What. a sex video of Imogen Conrad?
How do you know it's gonna leak?
I don't. Been tipped off that it might.
When did you last hear from echo?
It's possible Moscow
knows we're watching Igor.
Your little lenochka was spying on us.
Can you authorise a team to extract her?
It's too risky. Kate. I'm
not leaving her there. Rose.
I'm really sorry. but I have
to go away again tomorrow.
It's a potentially hostile environment.
Everything is in place.
Now you are going to find
out what Anderson knows.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
'Sorry.' no need.
I told you it was your choice.
'Sorry that I'm late. I made
the cab stop for a coffee.'
You're a good girl. Lena.
Going to morning mass.
Right?
Say it for mic.
I'm a good girl going to morning mass.
Perfect. Let's go.
Clear sky.
Ok...
'How's the weather?' It's still cloudy here.
Minutes.
I hope.
Hostile in church.
Yes.
Get in! All right.
We're in business. Clear sky.
Exit street clear but
assume hostile still in church.
In position and clear.
Amber position in five.
Car approaching.
Market place location.
Car parked in the usual place.
Lena.
You know what to do.
Eyes on echo. She's on the approach.
Possible tail. blue shirt.
Oui. bonjour. J'appelle Sylvia.
Tail has dropped off.
Second tail. Red baseball cap. on foot.
Following her up republic.
Confirm tail two.
'Green positions.'
Take out tail two in five seconds.
Lena. Come on. I've got you.
Get in.
Fuck.
You're safe.
Come on! Come on. come on.
Fuck!
Fuck.
'Are you all right? The team?'
yeah. We made it to sicily.
I'm sorry.
'I know what it's like to lose an agent.'
We'll talk when you're back.
Hello. you.
Looks like you've been in a war.
I have. What. something bad happened?
I lost someone. My love.
I'm so sorry.
So am I.
What. do you wanna...
Do you wanna talk about it?
Can you talk about it?
No.
But you ok?
I'm alive. Yeah.
Come here. Come here.
There you go.
All right. Got you now.
You look rested.
Ditto.
I've got something to show you.
I've found the Russian ops team.
They flew Moscow to
Istanbul on their real passports
the day before we arrived in Malta.
Used three different credit cards.
but they're all linked to
the same billing address.
which is a known svr back office.
Well. they're not as
clever as they think. No.
No. I figured they'd switch to
aliases once they got to Istanbul.
so I looked up anyone who paid in cash.
Simonov. smirnov.
Palachnikov. kuznetsov.
That's more than stupid.
That's totally reckless.
What is? They travelled on old aliases.
It's unheard of for Moscow centre
to take risks using worn passports.
Unless you're in a massive rush. Yeah.
So... bottom line.
They didn't know about our op
until the day before yesterday.
Which means someone must
have tipped them off about echo.
Yeah. Who? Someone
who knows about our op.
Can you send this to
zak and Rose? Yeah.
Do you want a coffee?
Er. no. I'm good. thanks.
I warned you that going
back might end in disaster.
I know you did.
We spent all night swimming
in a river of Maltese ministry shit.
Next time we trigger a shoot-out
around church-going civilians.
they'd rather we asked first!
I'm sorry.
But shouldn't they be
blaming the Russians?
I know you wanted to save your agent.
But you were lucky to get out
alive. It wasn't just luck. zak.
Can't we just agree this proves
Moscow was trying to stop our op
to protect their asset in London?
Go on.
Igor rushed his team
out on well-known aliases.
ignoring all their protocols.
That's a man that's desperate
to protect a high-stakes operation.
You think he found out
we bugged his villa. How?
Well. why would he be moving
an ops team out in such a panic?
So he was tipped off?
I think so. From London?
It's a possibility. And their aim
was to kill you as well as echo?
Reduce the Russia desk to ground zero?
It's crude. but they
might think it was worth it
if their London op was
big enough. which it is.
It's a possibility.
But let's say Moscow fed you the idea
that they've got an
asset here in the cabinet.
Isn't this exactly what they'd do?
Set you up. aim close.
A near miss. just enough
to make you believe
they were trying to kill you.
Or they were trying to take me out
to stop my op and get their
asset into downing street.
It's plausible. We have
to acknowledge that.
Look. this isn't just about
what happened in Valletta.
Rav and I have found credible grounds
for suspecting both Ryan
Walker and Imogen Conrad.
What? Are you serious?
The pm expressly forbade us
from investigating his ministers.
I know. but I had to...
No buts! Jesus. Kate.
When you breach a
direct order from the pm.
you put the entire service in jeopardy!
He didn't leave us any
choice! He's the prime minister!
I will have to take this upstairs.
To the foreign secretary?
Right now. there's a strong chance
he'll be the next prime minister. zak.
But a slim one he's a Russian asset.
And if he is. then it'll be too
late to do anything about this.
Our democracy is more
important than your suspicions.
We need to get echo.
Lena's brother. out of Russia.
We owe him that much at least.
I wasn't going to tell you today.
Our team lost alexei in st Petersburg.
Lost him? Moscow got there first.
I'm sorry.
You did all you could.
But right now. we've got bigger problems.
We do if zak keeps
sidelining my intelligence.
If he won't do it. then I
will talk to sir Alan and...
And the pm myself.
You cannot go behind his back.
You're in enough trouble as it
is. and you're not thinking straight.
You need time to process
everything. What time?
In a few days. we might have a
Russian asset running the country.
For all we know. Igor's tip-off
about Lena came from our side.
Get some rest. Then we'll talk.
He must resign. anushka.
But he won't. will he? He must.
He met with our political
enemy off the books.
without his protection
officers or officials present.
That's the kind of naked corruption
we expect from the opposition.
It's inexplicable. and it's inexcusable.
So just to be clear.
are you accusing the foreign secretary
of collusion with the kremlin?
I'm saying he has no principles.
and that populist rhetoric he's spouting
could have been written in Moscow.
He's not fit for public
office. And what about you?
If you behaved inappropriately.
would you resign?
I've not met with the
Russian foreign minister
off the record. have I?
That wasn't my question.
I'm trying to understand what
your moral code is in the case of...
No. no. I'm sorry. anushka.
I'm not gonna engage in hypotheticals.
Fucking itv. They're worse than the beeb.
What the hell was that
"moral code" bullshit all about?
She was just trying
to get under your skin.
Yeah. but with what? Felt
like she had something on me.
No. Trust me. if they thought
they had anything on you.
I would know about it.
Did you find out whether
Kate and her team
were looking into this krimsov business?
Nope. I haven't asked. And
she wouldn't tell me anyway.
Come on. Unsupervised contact
with the Russian foreign minister
in the middle of a war?
Yeah. I agree. it fucking stinks.
Yeah. so can't she throw us a crumb?
If we knew Ryan was
being investigated by sis.
we could finally drive a
stake through his heart.
Listen. I am not gonna push her on it.
She's under enough
pressure as it is. ok?
With what?
She can't say. can she?
And the alternative is what?
Ryan as prime minister?
Look. if we give the nod
that sis are investigating
Ryan's links with Moscow.
then it will land on Kate. won't it?
I can't do it. I'm sorry. I can't. All right.
Well. call all the cabinet spads.
You tell them Meg. Ted and I
are gonna release a
joint statement tonight
calling for Ryan's resignation.
If we can get enough ministers
to join us. he'll have to resign.
Ok. All right.
He's got no further comments.
Mel. is he gonna resign?
What do you think?
Can you get that? I don't want
my morning face everywhere.
Shit. What's up?
Mylar might be headed
for administration.
They just fired John. Does
it mention your investment?
No. thank god.
Please tell me you are bringing
some good news this morning. Melissa.
I could really. really do with it.
I came to tell you I'm resigning.
Now? In the middle of my campaign?
I'm sorry. I just don't think
our values align any more.
I assume you value honesty.
Absolutely. Good.
So did you tell the press about
Ryan's meeting with krimsov?
Of course I didn't.
I'm glad to hear it.
because nobody in Whitehall
wants to hire a snitch.
Resignation accepted. then.
Maybe it's for the best.
Well. good luck.
I really hope it's a fair fight.
This is politics. there's
nothing fair about it.
What. like ruining Imogen Conrad's life?
For... I'm not gonna
use the video. Melissa.
He means we've got no
idea what you're talking about.
But in case there's any doubt.
remember you're still bound
by the nda in your contract.
Tell me something.
Did Dmitri krimsov really lose a child?
Or did you make it up
to save face? Get out!
God.
It's ok. It's ok. It's ok.
We'll...
We'll survive. I just need to
weather this mylar cluster fuck!
Can't your dad help you out
again? I don't know. I don't know.
Maybe. I don't know. I just...
Sorry. It's just... It's just a lot. all at once.
Do people really think we'd use
our son as a get-out-of-jail-free card?
No. No. Come on.
Of course they don't.
You know I suffer too.
You've got a funny way of showing it.
Well. I had to put the story to bed.
When we're in number ten...
That's your dream. it's not mine.
Well. we agreed it'd be a new
chapter for us both. Did we?
Or did you just assume
that we'd stumble on
in the service of your career?
You know I'll wait.
For what?
For you to come back.
At least you've got your ambition.
That's something to hold on to.
I said I'd help to try to get us there.
Then we can think again.
So you'd better go
and butter up your dad.
I've spoken to every single spad.
All of their ministers are
complete cowards. bar none.
Thank you very much.
So. as of now. all we have
is you. Meg and dear old Ted.
Now. trust me...
Three cabinet resignations
does not a rebellion make.
Tell them if Ryan wins.
he's gonna clean the stables.
So most of them won't have
jobs... Or a party to speak of.
Well. we definitely need
more than three of you.
Ok. try them again.
I'll call some of the principals myself.
We'll tell them Meg. Ted and I
are gonna come out just
before the news at ten tonight.
Ok.
We need to know why
lev amatov wanted Imogen
at the Montenegro conference.
'Right. and who she
was hanging out with.'
according to Angela white. she was
"horsing around" with Joshua long.
'Ok. so maybe he was the go-between?'
or the honey trap. Maybe lev
has some kind of hold on her.
and long could be the reason why.
I'll see you later.
Kate Henderson. Yes.
Hi. I'm Joshua long. How are
you? You wanted to see me?
Yes. I'm sorry to bother you. It's all right.
I work for the foreign office. Yeah.
I wanted to have a word with you
about your time working
with Imogen Conrad.
What did Stuart tell you about it?
This has got nothing to do with him.
Well. I left politics last year.
So I'm not sure how
much help I can really be.
Not even in the interest
of national security?
Right.
Let's start with your visit to Montenegro.
What about it?
Well. it's been alleged that you and
Imogen were having an affair there.
What? Who the fuck told you that?
Who are you really?
I've never been
unfaithful in my marriage.
let alone with Imogen.
So why did you leave her
office shortly after the trip?
Lev amatov had been
sniffing around her for a while.
He was the one who
invited her to the conference.
Why did he want her there? No idea.
He kept her pretty busy
with meet and greets.
so I wasn't invited.
After Stuart got ill.
I was the one who had to sit
through all the conference talks.
which was a pointless exercise.
So this alleged affair...
Yeah. I've told you all I know.
So I've gotta go now.
Well. if you "remember"
anything else. just... yeah.
You know how to find me. yeah?
Jamie's come good.
That's six cabinet rebels
with a cause. Melissa?
Are you selling some intel.
or are you suing for peace?
I've resigned.
Welcome to the Ryan
resistance movement.
Please tell me you've got
some dynamite in that bag.
Got some information.
but... You're not gonna like it.
Ok. Spit it out. I'm a big girl.
Ryan says that he's
managed to get his hands
on some compromising footage of you.
What kind of footage?
Nobody's seen it. Apparently.
it was filmed in a hotel room.
And you're with a man
who isn't your husband.
Look. assuming that it does exist...
what I'd do is I would get out ahead of it.
Warn the public that there's
a fake porn video in circulation
before someone releases it
and tries to claim that it's real.
Will it make any difference?
Once it's out. it's out.
People can't UN-see things. fake or not.
I know. I know. but I actually
think that the public will sympathise.
I mean. Russia's well known
for churning out crap like this.
Can't believe this is happening.
Look. I told Ryan that
he'd be mad to leak it.
I mean. he'd be the first person
that everyone will suspect.
And he... he claimed
he agreed with me. guys.
But you think he'll do it anyway?
It depends how desperate he gets.
Well. I think he's gonna
be pretty fucking desperate
when he finds out we're
trying to oust him from the race.
Fuck.
Imogen. what are you thinking?
Phone Meg. Ted. the others.
Tell them we're gonna
hold off on the joint statement
for 24 hours for tactical reasons.
Ok. And then what?
I need to see Ryan.
Maybe he'll chose his humanity
over his ambition for once.
Ok. let's attack this one now.
Very nice. Very nice.
You can't even fucking call me yourself.
I just asked the campaign team to
schedule a meeting in my diary. dad.
I've heard the construction
firm's about to go bust.
Yeah. well. it looked like a
solid investment at the time.
Yeah. if you'd come and worked for me.
you wouldn't have had to go
grubbing about in the margins.
What the hell do you
know about property?
Look. is there any way that we could
have this conversation face to face?
Obvious bloody hindrance.
Look. I need to plug a hole in the deal.
If it gets out I'm involved. I'm finished.
It's not a good look for a labour mp. is it?
Building luxury flats on a union car park.
Either way. I can't go into
downing street bankrupt. dad.
How much do you need?
A million. It's a loan.
You'll get your interest.
You get into bed with the devil. son.
and he eventually fucks you so
hard you can hear your teeth rattle.
So. what's the answer?
Well. come up for the
ceremony. like I asked you.
I can't. I'm in the middle of a campaign.
Aren't they your voters?
If you want me to bail you out
of a hole. you need to work for it.
Fuck. How long was I out?
Long enough for me
to find an agent report
from the Montenegro
conference. Guess who was there?
I don't know. Igor borodin.
Close. Kyril markov.
What? At the same
time as Imogen? Yeah.
"Agent recognised
kyril markov in audience"
"at delegate welcome address."
"Identification verified."
It's a hell of a coincidence.
Yeah. I mean. do we think
Imogen knew who he was?
I've no idea.
But if she didn't then. she might do now.
I've gotta go and see Stuart and the kids.
I'll see you. yeah? Yeah.
Hello. my love. Hiya.
Your priest says that you must
drink before your confession.
Confession or absolution?
Depends what you need. I suppose.
Cheers. Cheers.
That helped.
Do you know what? I actually
nicked a cheeky packet of fags
from an intern at work.
Got a lighter here somewhere.
Was that cigarettes? Absolutely not.
You two are such fucking hypocrites.
Don't swear. Fiona. See what I mean?
You ok?
I'll survive.
Yeah?
Do you wanna talk about what
happened on your last trip. or...?
I was trying to extract an agent...
and she was killed on the way out.
Ok.
Were you hurt. or...? Not physically.
But are you safe now
here? Are we safe?
The kids and everything? Ok. listen.
Moscow has never tried to take
out a British agent on home turf. ok?
Let alone their families.
Are you sure?
That convention has been
in place since the cold war.
There is nothing to suggest
that they would breach it. right?
It's just that you recently said
that the rules of the game
have changed. so I'm just a little...
I've gotta go. Sixth-floor summons.
I'm sorry. love. All right. All right.
Evening. Take a seat.
I'm very sorry for the situation I created.
But I hope you can
agree I had no choice.
Kate...
you've been suspended.
On what grounds?
Do we really need to spell it out?
Yes. please.
Ignoring a direct instruction.
Putting your team at
risk without due cause.
The foreign secretary is
insisting you stand down.
In two days' time. we
might have a Russian asset
in downing street...
Nobody doubts your integrity.
But. what. we're going
to just let it happen
in case their exposure
damages our democracy?
The only fact here is you
ignored a direct order from the pm.
I'm afraid you put us in a
very difficult position. Kate.
First. the krimsov leak.
Now this diplomatic
firestorm around Malta.
The foreign secretary is furious.
So the minister that might be
working for Moscow wants me gone.
and we'll just roll over?
Bury my intelligence
because it's too inconvenient?
I hope you know me better than
that. This is a temporary measure.
But we'll follow our own
line of enquiry from here.
So echo was just collateral damage?
The life of a vulnerable young woman
was an incredible stake to gamble with.
God. you can be a
heartless bastard. zak.
It's the truth. and you know it.
I need my head of the Russia desk
to know where to draw a bloody line
and when to see the bigger
picture. Enough. both of you.
You'll have the opportunity
to make your case
at the board of inquiry. both you and rav.
Not rav. He was following my orders.
Your orders weren't authorised.
Is there anything else you want to say?
No.
I'll save it for the inquiry. Good night.
I've told security to sign you out.
Thanks for coming in.
It's all good. What happened?
We're both suspended.
I think zak would have fired me
then if c hadn't stayed his hand.
I'm sorry.
Man. fuck them.
All right? While you was
up there talking to the suits.
I did some more digging around
the Montenegro conference.
Those are the flight logs
from all the closest airports
over the two days before
the conference started.
You wanna guess who else was
rubbing shoulders with the delegates?
Our very own zak Hussein.
Can... can you place him in portonovi?
He flew to Dubrovnik. and
then hired a car with hertz.
I even tracked his office phone ip
to a little cafe near the conference
centre on the day it started
cos his stupid little vpn dropped out.
Zak in situ with Imogen
and kyril markov? Yeah.
Could be. I mean. do they know
each other. zak and Imogen?
Fuck knows. She's
never mentioned him.
Well. if he's there.
then theoretically. it
could be Imogen. not Ryan.
in Moscow's pocket.
With zak helping her?
The man who learned of our op
the day echo's cover was blown?
Well. that confirms it.
then. We're on our own.
Subtitles by accessibility@itv.Com
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm